Guide to the Ramón Hernández Tejano Music Collection
The Wittliff Collections
- Artist Files, 1922-2019, undated
  - Female Artist Files
    - Trini Rincon, [2014], undated (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Rio Grande, undated (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Gloria Rios - Photographs (photocopied), 1946-1964, undated (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Gloria Rios - Events, 2002, 2007 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Gloria Rios - Ramón Hernández material, 2005, undated (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Gloria Rios - Research, 2005, undated (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Gloria Rios - Clippings, 2005, 2007, undated (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Gloria Rios - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Raquel Rivas, 1994, undated (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Lorrina Robinson, undated (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Edna Rodarte, 2014, 2018, undated (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Lupita Rodela, 1980-2000, undated (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Blanca "Blanca Rosa" Rodríguez, 1964-2016, undated (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Carrie Rodriguez, 2017 (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Cassandra Rodriguez, 1985-1989, undated (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Dody Rodriguez, undated (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Janie Rodriguez, 2001Leticia Rodriguez (Box 119, Folder 18)
    - Leticia Rodriguez, 2013 (Box 119, Folder 19)
    - Sandy Rodriguez, 2015, undated (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - Beatriz Rojas, undated (Box 119, Folder 21)
    - Laura Rojas, 2011, undated (Box 119, Folder 22)
    - Anna Roman, 1994, undated (Box 119, Folder 23)
    - Anna Roman - Clippings, 1991, 1995, undated (Box 119, Folder 24)
    - Ernestine Romero, undated (Box 119, Folder 25)
    - Rosalba, undated (Box 119, Folder 26)
    - Rosalicia, 2003 (Box 119, Folder 27)
    - Isis Marie Rosario, 2004 (Box 119, Folder 28)
    - Amber Rose, 1997-1999, undated (Box 119, Folder 29)
    - Amber Rose - Clippings, 1996, undated (Box 119, Folder 30)
    - Ashlee Rose, 2014 (Box 119, Folder 31)
    - Tori Rose, undated (Box 119, Folder 32)
    - Roxanne, undated (Box 119, Folder 33)
    - Roxanne - Clippings, 1995-2015, undated (Box 119, Folder 34)
    - Lydia Rubio, 1983, undated (Box 119, Folder 35)
    - Belen Ruby, 2018 (Box 119, Folder 36)
    - Elizabeth Ruiz, 1982-1986 (Box 119, Folder 37)
    - Elizabeth Ruiz - Clippings, 1985-2018, undated (Box 119, Folder 38)
    - Valentina Ruiz, 2013 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Ruth, undated (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Ilyssa Saenz, 2011, undated (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Sylvia Saenz, 1995 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Adeline Salas, 1987, undated (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Patty Salas, undated (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Sheri Salas, undated (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Laura Salazar, undated (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Monica Saldívar, 2015, undated (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Yolanda Saldivar, 1995-1996, undated (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Lidia San Miguel, 2003 (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Amanda Sanchez, 2016 (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Anna Sánchez, undated (Box 120, Folder 13)
    - Emma Sanchez, 2016 (Box 120, Folder 14)
    - Irene Sanchez, undated (Box 120, Folder 15)
    - Isabel Marie Sánchez, 2017, undated (Box 120, Folder 16)
    - Isabel Marie Sánchez- Clippings, 2013-2016 (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - Isabel Marie Sánchez - Clippings, 2017, undated (Box 120, Folder 18)
    - Jessica Sanchez, undated (Box 120, Folder 19)
    - Amalia Sandez, undated (Box 120, Folder 20)
    - Rina Sandoval, 1999-2000, undated (Box 120, Folder 21)
    - Sangre Latina, 2001 (Box 120, Folder 22)
    - Santa, undated (Box 120, Folder 23)
    - Santa - Ramón Hernández material, 1986, undated (Box 120, Folder 24)
    - Santa - Clippings, 1983, 1986, undated (Box 120, Folder 25)
    - Blanca Santos - Photographs, undated (Box 120, Folder 26)
    - Blanca Santos - Ramón Hernández material, 1987-1988, undated (Box 120, Folder 27)
    - Blanca Santos - Clippings, 1987-1990, undated (Box 120, Folder 28)
    - Sapphire, 2011 (Box 120, Folder 29)
    - Saraly y La Promesa, 2013-2014, undated (Box 120, Folder 30)
    - Saraly y La Promesa - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 120, Folder 31)
    - Sarina y Los Dukes, 2001, undated (Box 120, Folder 32)
    - Sarina y Los Dukes - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 120, Folder 33)
    - Cacy Savala, 2013, undated (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Cacy Savala - Clippings, 2012-2018, undated (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Savannah, 2013, 2015, undated (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Selena - Photographs, 1987-1988, undated (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Selena - Publicity photographs, 1996-1999, undated (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Selena - Mounted photographs (1 of 8), undated (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Selena - Mounted photographs (2 of 8), undated (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Selena - Mounted photographs (3 of 8), undated (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Selena - Mounted photographs (4 of 8), undated (Box 122, Folder 1)
    - Selena - Mounted photographs (5 of 8), undated (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - Selena - Mounted photographs (6 of 8), undated (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - Selena - Mounted photographs (7 of 8), undated (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - Selena - Mounted photographs (8 of 8), undated (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - Selena - Personal, undated (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Selena - Concerts and events:, 1991-2005, undated (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - Selena - Album covers and liner notes, 1989-1996, undated (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - Selena - Mounted record cover, undated (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Selena - Mounted cassette covers, 1984-1995, undated (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Selena - Mounted Selena y Dinos CD Covers, 1994, undated (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Selena - Mounted Selena CD Covers, 1989-1993 (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Selena - Mounted Selena CD Covers, 1994-1995 (Box 123, Folder 8)
    - Selena - Mounted Selena CD Covers, 1995, undated (Box 123, Folder 9)
    - Selena - Mounted Selena CD Covers, undated (Box 124, Folder 1)
    - Selena - Mounted Various Artists/Compilations CD Covers, 1992-1995 (Box 124, Folder 2)
    - Selena - Mounted Various Artists/Compilations CD Covers, 1995, undated (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Selena - Mounted Various Artists/Compilations CD Covers (1 of 2), undated (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Selena - Mounted Various Artists/Compilations CD Covers (2 of 2), undated (Box 124, Folder 5)
    - Selena - Album publicity, 1995, undated (Box 124, Folder 6)
    - Selena -Publicity, 1990, 1996, undated (Box 124, Folder 7)
    - Selena - Business correspondence, 1988-1995, undated (Box 124, Folder 8)
    - Selena - Ramón Hernández material (1 of 4), 1989-2000, undated (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Selena - Ramón Hernández material (2 of 4), 1985-[1995], undated (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Selena - Ramón Hernández material (3 of 4), undated (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Selena - Ramón Hernández material (4 of 4), 1995 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - Selena - Memorial material, undated (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - Selena - Selena Film Production, 1996 (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Selena - Clippings, 1987-1994 (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Selena - Clippings, February-April 9, 1995 (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Selena - Clippings, April 10-May 1995 (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Selena - Clippings, June-September 1995 (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Selena - Clippings, October-December 1995 (Box 125, Folder 6)
    - Selena - Clippings, 1996 (Box 125, Folder 7)
    - Selena - Clippings, 1997-2005 (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Selena - Clippings, 2006-2018 (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Selena - Clippings, undated (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - Selena - Magazine clippings, 1991-2015 (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Selena - Magazine clippings, undated (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Selena - Mounted clippings, 1985-March 1989 (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Selena - Mounted clippings, April 1989-1991 (Box 126, Folder 1)
    - Selena - Mounted clippings, undated (Box 126, Folder 2)
    - Selena - Cassettes, 1984-[1995] (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Selena - DVDs, 2003 (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Selena - Promotional Materials, [2011], undated (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Selena - Books (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Selena - Books (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 126, Folder 7)
    - Selena - Books (3 of 3), 1997 (Box 126, Folder 8)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Mounted photographs, undated (Box 127)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Mounted publicity photographs and artwork, 1995, undated (Box 128)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Calendars, 1990-1998 (Box 129)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Midsized clippings, 1991-1994 (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Midsized clippings, April 1995 (Box 130, Folder 2)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Midsized clippings, May-July 1995 (Box 130, Folder 3)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Midsized clippings, August-December 1995 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Midsized clippings, 1996 (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Midsized clippings, 1997-2000 (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Midsized clippings, 2001-2010, undated (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Magazine clippings, 1993-1995, undated (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Oversized clippings, 1993-1994 (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Oversized clippings, April 1-April 2, 1995 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Oversized clippings, April 3-8, 1995 (Box 131, Folder 3)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Oversized clippings, April 9-September 1995 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Oversized clippings, October-December 1995 (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Oversized clippings, 1996-2004 (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Oversized clippings, 2005-2018 (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Mounted clippings, 1997-1994 (Box 132)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Mounted clippings, 1995 (Box 133)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Mounted clippings, 1995 (Box 134)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Mounted clippings, undated (Box 135)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Magazines, 1990-1995 (Box 136)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Magazines, 1996-2005 (Box 137)
    - Selena - Oversized material - Magazines, 2011, 2015, undated (Box 138)
    - Selena - Oversized materials - Selena Etc. Boutique, 1996, undated (Box 140)
    - Selena - Oversized materials - LP covers, 1986-1990, undated (Box 141)
    - Selena - Audiovisual material - CDs, 1992-2004, undatd (Box 141)
    - Selena - Audiovisual material - Videocassettes, 1994-1999, undated (Box 142)
    - Sensacion, undated (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Mary Lou Serna - Photographs, 1985, undated (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Mary Lou Serna - Personal, undated (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Mary Lou Serna - Ramón Hernández material, undated (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Mary Lou Serna - Clippings, 1995, undated (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - CeCe Segarra, 2010 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Sesi, 2006 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Chelo Silva, 1988-2003, undated (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Simply Rayne, undated (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Sin Igual, undated (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Sindy, undated (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Sirenas del Caribe, 1989, undated (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Sisters Morales, 1993-2016, undated (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Sylvia Sol - Photographs, undated (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Sylvia Sol, undated (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - Sylvia Sol - Ramón Hernández material, 1986, undated (Box 143, Folder 16)
    - Sylvia Sol - Clippings, 1986, undated (Box 143, Folder 17)
    - Maria Soledad, 2001-2002, undated (Box 143, Folder 18)
    - Maria Soledad - Audiovisual material, 2001 (Box 143, Folder 19)
    - [Jania] Solis, undated (Box 143, Folder 20)
    - Rachel Solis, 1989, undated (Box 143, Folder 21)
    - Sonrisas, undated (Box 143, Folder 22)
    - Soundrave, 2009, undated (Box 143, Folder 23)
    - Sugarjammer, undated (Box 143, Folder 24)
    - Sunny (Laura Youngs), undated (Box 143, Folder 25)
    - Sunny (Laura Youngs) - Clippings, 2011-2012 (Box 143, Folder 26)
    - Sweetmeat, 2012 (Box 143, Folder 27)
    - Norma T., [1994]-1995, undated (Box 143, Folder 28)
    - T-Max, 1995 (Box 143, Folder 29)
    - Taboo, undated (Box 143, Folder 30)
    - Esmi Talamantez, 1995, undated (Box 143, Folder 31)
    - Tejano Rose, 2016, undated (Box 143, Folder 32)
    - Tempest, undated (Box 143, Folder 33)
    - Las Tesoros de San Antonio - Mounted photographs, undated (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Las Tesoros de San Antonio, 2011, undated (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Las Tesoros de San Antonio - Clippings, 2010-2018, undated (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Las Tesoros de San Antonio - Audiovisual material, 2015-2017 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Rosetta Tharpe, undated (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Tina y Los Gallitos, 2003, 2005 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Topo Chica, 2016 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Agnes Torres, 2010 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Christina Torres, undated (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Crystal Torres, 2013-2014, undated (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Patsy Torres - Photographs (1 of 2), 1983-1989, undated (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Patsy Torres - Photographs (2 of 2), 1983-1989, undated (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Patsy Torres - Photographs - Torres' Wedding, 1988 (Box 144, Folder 13)
    - Patsy Torres - Publicity photographs, undated (Box 144, Folder 14)
    - Patsy Torres - Personal, undated (Box 144, Folder 15)
    - Patsy Torres - Concerts and events, 1986-2013, undated (Box 144, Folder 16)
    - Patsy Torres -Album covers, undated (Box 144, Folder 17)
    - Pasty Torres - Mounted CD covers, undated (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Pasty Torres - Publicity, 1989-1998, undated (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Pasty Torres - Proclamations and tributes, 1989-1990 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Pasty Torres - Business records, 1988, 1998, undated (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Pasty Torres - Ramón Hernández material, 1985-1991, undated (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Pasty Torres - Clippings, 1984-1987 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Pasty Torres - Clippings, 1988 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Pasty Torres - Clippings, 1989 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Pasty Torres - Clippings, 1990-1997 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Pasty Torres - Clippings, 2000-2009 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Pasty Torres - Clippings, 2010-2014 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Pasty Torres - Clippings, 2015-2018 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Pasty Torres - Clippings, undated (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Pasty Torres - Clippings, undated (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Pasty Torres - Magazines, 1986-2013, undated (Box 145, Folder 15)
    - Patsy Torres - Audiovisual material (1 of 2), 1995, undated (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Patsy Torres - Audiovisual material (2 of 2), undated (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Patsy Torres - Promotional material, undated (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Susan Torres, undated (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Liz Torrez, 2000-2001, undated (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Liz Torrez - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Trinidad Pan Masters, 1990, undated (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Trío Sembradores, undated (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Trisha y Grupo Ritmo, undated (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Trisha y Grupo Ritmo - Clippings, 1995-2002, undated (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Jessica R. Trujillo, undated (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - The Uniques, 2013, 2014, undated (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Lynda V. & The Boys, 1994, undated (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Christina Marie Valdez, 2018 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Stephanie Valenzuela, undated (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Candace Vargas, [2007], 2013, undated (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - Deborah Vargas, 2007 (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Concha L. "Conchita" Vasquez, undated (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - Lala Vazquez, 2011 (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - Gina Vega, undated (Box 146, Folder 20)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs (1 of 2), 1998, undated (Box 146, Folder 21)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs (2 of 2), 1998, undated (Box 146, Folder 22)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs - CD Release Party, [1998] (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs - Muy Bien Taping with Albert Zamora, 1998 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs - Christmas Concert, undated (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs - Domingo Show, undated (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs - Fort Sam Houston Event, undated (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs - Lackland Air Force Base Event, undated (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs - Market Square Concert, undated (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs - Mexico, undated (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs - ¿Que Onda? Anniversary Party, undated (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs - La Rancherita and Friends Taping, undated (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs - Walmart Signing Event, undated (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs - 35mm negatives, undated (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Marlissa Vela - Photographs - Publicity photographs, undated (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Marlissa Vela - Concert and event publicity, 1998, undated (Box 147, Folder 14)
    - Marlissa Vela - Publicity, undated (Box 147, Folder 15)
    - Marlissa Vela - Business records, 1988 (Box 147, Folder 16)
    - Marlissa Vela - Ramón Hernández material, 1998-1999, undated (Box 147, Folder 17)
    - Marlissa Vela - Clippings, 1998, 2002, undated (Box 147, Folder 18)
    - Marlissa Vela - Magazine issues, 1998 (Box 147, Folder 19)
    - Marlissa Vela - Audiovisual material, 2005, undated (Box 147, Folder 20)
    - Las Venenosas, 1995, undated (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Veronica y Avance, 2010, undated (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Veronika, undated (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Victoria, 1993 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Victoria y Sus Chikos, undated (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Victoria y Sus Chikos - Clippings, 2001-2008 (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Victoria y Sus Chikos - Audiovisual material, undated (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Rita Vidaurri - Photographs, undated (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Rita Vidaurri - Mounted photographs and advertisements (1 of 2), undated (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Rita Vidaurri - Mounted photographs and advertisements (2 of 2), undated (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Rita Vidaurri - Personal, undated (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Rita Vidaurri - Concert and event publicity, 1990-2014 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Rita Vidaurri - Ramón Hernández material, 2000, undated (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Rita Vidaurri - Clippings (1 of 2), 1956-2013 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Rita Vidaurri - Clippings (2 of 2), 2014-2017, undated (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Rita Vidaurri - Audiovisual material, 1999-2014 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - Lolita Villa, 1983, 1985 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Gloria Villarreal, 2002 (Box 148, Folder 18)
    - Kristie Villarreal, undated (Box 148, Folder 19)
    - Andrea Villela, 2002 (Box 148, Folder 20)
    - Ella Vox, undated (Box 148, Folder 21)
    - Wendy & Meneo's, undated (Box 148, Folder 22)
    - Raquel "Rocky" Williams, undated (Box 148, Folder 24)
    - Xtasy, undated (Box 148, Folder 25)
    - Yadira, 2004 (Box 148, Folder 26)
    - E.V. Yama, 2016 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Yannel, 2006 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Eva Ybarra, 1988, undated (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Eva Ybarra - Clippings (1 of 2), 1991-2010 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Eva Ybarra - Clippings (2 of 2), 2011-2017 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Liza Ybarra, 2000-2017, undated (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Yvanna, undated (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Yve, undated (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Yvette, 2003, 2005 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Monica Yvette, 2000, 2011, undated (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Yvonne y Fuego, 2015, undated (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Lyric Zamora, undated (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - Norma Zenteno, 1993, undated (Box 149, Folder 13)
  - Oversized Artist Portraits - Male Artists
    - Ramon Ayala, undated (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Maxie Bustamante, undated (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Tony De La Rosa (2), undated (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Johnny Degollado, undated (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Manuel "Cowboy" Donley, undated (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Eligio Escobar, undated (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - The Galaxies (with Sunny Ozuna), undated (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Manuel Guerra, undated (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Salomé Gutiérrez, undated (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Carlos Guzmán (4), undated (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Johnny Herrera, undated (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Flaco Jimenez, undated (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Valerio Longoria, undated (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Isidro "El Indio" Lopez (2), undated (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Jacinto Lopez, undated (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Freddie Martinez (6), undated (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Narciso Martinez, undated (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Oscar Martinez, undated (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Joe Meija (with Lorena Meija), undated (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Leonard Montelongo, undated (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - José A. Morante, undated (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Bobby Naranjo, undated (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Emilio Navaira, undated (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Alfonso Ramos, undated (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Gilbert Rodriguez, undated (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - The Royal Jesters (2), undated (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Placido Salazar (5), undated (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Oscar Serrato, undated (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Sunglows (2, 1 with Joe Bravo), undated (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Sunny and the Sunliners, undated (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Ruben Vela (2), undated (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Juan Viesca (2), undated (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Beto Villa, undated (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - Nick Villarreal, undated (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Agapito Zuñiga, undated (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Oversized Artist Portraits - Female Artists
    - Laura Canales (2;1 with Augie Meyers, Ramón Hernández, David Lee Garza, and Simon "The Diamond" Molina, undated (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Linda Escobar, undated (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Pauline "Paula" Estrada (6), undated (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Rosita Fernandez (2), undated (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Ada Garcia, undated (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Shelly Lares (with Javier Galvan), undated (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Lydia Mendoza, undated (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Monica, undated (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Blanca "Blanca Rosa" Rodriguez (2), 2011, undated (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Patsy Torres (2), undated (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Marlissa Vela, undated (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Rita Vidaurri (2), undated (Box 155, Folder 6)
- Posters and Oversized Materials, 1948-2018, undated
  Series II: Posters and Oversized Materials, 1948-2018, undated Boxes 156-164 and map case drawers 36-44
  This series can be seen as a continuation of the Artists Files, but with material that does not fit in standard document boxes. There are two exceptions to this: the majority of boxes, including the oversized ones, for Little Joe Hernandez (boxes 33-46) and Selena (boxes 121-142) are housed within Series I: Artists Files due to the sheer quantity of material, but as with all artists, materials related to them can be found in many series.
  As mentioned, mounted posters are those adhered to foamcore for easier display, possibly for exhibit in Hernández's Hispanic Entertainment Archive.
  This series is divided into Artist Posters, Mounted Posters, Concert Posters, and Oversized Material
  • Artist Posters (boxes 156-161) are separated into male and female artists and then arranged alphabetically. The majority of the material found in the series are posters, advertisements and other publicity material, and LP record covers. Many are signed by the artist.
  • Oversized Posters are separated into male and female artists and arranged alphabetically and housed in map case drawers.
  • Concert Posters (161-163 and oversized) span 1948-2018 and are arranged chronologically. Oversized concert posters are housed in the map cases.